Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- General files, 1
  - Resolution Trust Corporation: Mark Up, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Federal Home Loan Bank Act; Resolution Trust Corporation Completion Act; Savings and Loans
  - Retired Military Cola, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Armed Services Committee
  - Revenue Reconciliation, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    Budget Deficit; Revenue Reconciliation Bill; Income Tax; Democratic Party
  - Risk Assessments, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Rivers, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Bureau of Land Management; Idaho--Rivers; Wild and Scenic Rivers; Bruneau River; Jarbidge River; Snake River; Salmon River
  - Rock Creek Bill, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    Federal Power Act; Hydropower; Rock Creek, California
    H.R. 649; H.R.231
  - Rocket Propellant/ Fuel Object Near Earth, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    INEL; Nuclear Fuel; NASA; Space Travel
  - Romania, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Rostenkowski, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Congressional Post Office
    Rostenkowski, Dan
  - Rural Communications, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    Rural Development; Cable Television; Rural Communication Systems
  - Rural Communities, 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    Tourist Trade; Economic Growth; Idaho--Rural Development; Community Development--Environmental Aspects
  - Rural Drinking Water, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    Idaho--Rural Development; Idaho--Water Quality
  - Rural Electrification Administration, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Rural Electrification Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    Rural Development; Agriculture
  - Rural Health Care, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    Rural Health Services
  - Rural Health Care: Telemedicine, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    Medical Care; Rural Health Services
  - Rural Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    Idaho Rural Development Council; Congressional Rural Caucus; Rural Development
  - Rural Medicine, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    Public Health; Rural Development; Rural Telemedicine Development Act; Telecommunications
    S.1088
  - Rural Policy Research Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Rural Telephone Company, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    Rural Development; Rural Electrification Administration
    Martell, Jim
  - Russian Aid, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Russian Loan Defaults, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    International Affairs
  - Russian Officer Housing Resettlement, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    International Relations; Veterans; Russia; Soviet Union
  - Safe Drinking Water Act, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    Western Water Caucus
    H.R.3392; H.R.4602
  - Safe Drinking Water Act, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    H.R.3392
  - Salmon, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    Bonneville Power Administration; Columbia River; Snake River; Idaho--Dams
  - Salmon, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Salmon: Agriculture, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    Bureau of Reclamation; Endangered Species Act; Water Rights; Water Resources
  - Resolution Reform Act, 1992 (Box 41)
    Banks and Banking; Securities and Exchange Commission; Securities Reform Act
    H.R.3227; S.1699
  - Salmon: Aluminum, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Water Resources; Bonneville Power Administration
  - Salmon: Andrus Plan, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Snake River; Valbois, The Resort; Drawdowns
  - Salmon: Andrus Plan, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Subcommittee on Environment and Natural Resources; Drawdowns
    Anrus, Cecil D.
  - Salmon: Army Corps, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Columbia River; Army Corps of Engineers; Bonneville Power Administration; Drawdown
  - Salmon: Background, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Salmon: Barging, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Salmon--Transportation
  - Salmon: Bonneville Power Administration, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Columbia Basin; Streamflow
  - Salmon: Bull Trout, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Sandpoint, Idaho; Lake Pend Oreille
  - Salmon: Bureau of Land Management, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Nez Perce Forest
  - Salmon: Bureau of Reclamation, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Salmon: Canada and United States On Salmon, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    United States--Canada Pacific Salmon Treaty; Pacific Ocean--Fishing; Trout Unlimited
  - Salmon: Cascade Reservoir, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Bureau of Reclamation; Drawdowns
  - Salmon: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Idaho Rivers Unlimited; Idaho Steelhead and Salmon Unlimited; Constituent Communication
  - Salmon: Correspondence: Idaho, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Constituent Communications
  - Salmon: Definition Of Species, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Salmon: Disease, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    Bonneville Power Administration
  - Salmon: Drawdown Test-Biological, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    Lower Granite Dam; Draft Enviromental Impact Statement
  - Salmon: Drawdowns, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    National Marine Fisheries Service
  - Salmon: Dworshak Dam, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    Drawdowns
  - Salmon: Federal Money, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    Appropriations; Drawdowns
    Brown, Ron
  - Salmon: Federal Rulings, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Salmon--Judgements
    Marsh, Malcolm F.
  - Salmon: Flows, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    Irrigation; Drawdowns; Snake River; Columbia River
  - Salmon: Habitat, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    Snake River Basin; Columbia River Basin
  - Salmon: Habitat, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    Oregon Rivers Council; Pacific Rivers Council
  - Salmon: Habitat, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    National Marine Fisheries; National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration
  - Salmon: Hanford, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    Columbia River; Aquaculture; University of Idaho
  - Salmon: Harvest, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    Salmon--Fisheries; Salmon Industry
  - Salmon: Irrigation, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    Milner Dam; Bureau of Reclamation
  - Salmon: Lake Pend Oreille, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    Drawdowns; Kokanee
  - Salmon: LaRocco Position, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    Salmon Recovery Working Group; Secretary of Commerce; Drawdowns
    Brown, Ronald H.
  - Salmon: Larry LaRocco Effort, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    Idaho--Political Activity
  - Salmon: Listings/Status, 1991-1994 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    National Marine Fisheries Service; Endangered Species
  - Salmon: Magnuson Act, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    Alaska--Fisheries; Magnuson Act; Marine Fish Conservation; Regional Fishery Management Councils Ethics Act
    H.R.4404; H.R.4713
  - Salmon: Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    Salmon--Transportation; Fishing Guides; Fisheries--Pacific Ocean
    Baucus, Max; Church, Frank
  - Salmon: Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    Pacific Rivers Council; Salmon--Habitat; Fishing--Pacific Ocean
  - Salmon: Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    Northwest Power Planning Council; Columbia River Basin
  - Salmon: Miscellaneous: Letters and Reports, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    United States--Canada Pacific Salmon Treaty; Endangered Species Act; Nez Perce Indians; Shoshone-Bannock Indians
  - Salmon: Miscellaneous; Newspaper Articles, 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    Drawdowns; Sturgeon; Indians of North America--Salmon Fisheries; Columbia River System
  - Salmon: Montana, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    Hungry Horse Reservoir; Libby Reservoir
  - Salmon: Navigation, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Columbia River Alliance for Fish and Commerce; Columbia River Basin
  - Salmon: Net Pen, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    Kiepke, George; Reandeau, George
  - Salmon: Northwest Power Planning Council, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Salmon: Outfitters, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    Fishing Guides
  - Salmon: Pacfish, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    Logging; Forest Service; Salmon--Habitat; Salmon--Fisheries; Nez Perce National Forest
    Kempthorne, Dirk
  - Salmon: Pacific Ocean, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    Fishing--Pacific Ocean
  - Salmon: Pipeline, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    Woodworth, Dick; Boylan, Delmar
  - Salmon: Plan Comparisons, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    Idaho Rivers United
  - Salmon: Position Papers, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Salmon: Power Companies, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    Pacific Northwest Utilities Conference Committee; Columbia River Basin; Idaho Power Company
  - Salmon: Press Coverage, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Salmon: Press Coverage, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Columbia River Basin; Endangered Species Act
  - Salmon: Recovery Program, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    Columbia River Inter-Tribal Fish Commission; Indians of North America--Salmon Fisheries
  - Salmon: Republican Views, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    Craig, Larry; Kempthorne, Dirk; Chenoweth, Helen
  - Salmon: Research, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    University of Idaho; Oregon State University; Washington State University; Columbia River System
  - Salmon: Shad/"Squaw Fish", 1994 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Salmon: Spills, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    Salmon--Diseases; Elwha River, Washington
  - Salmon: Steelhead, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Salmon: Sturgeon, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Salmon: Sturgeon, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 59)
    Indians fo North America--Fisheries; Nez Perce Indians; Wilderness Areas
  - Salmon: Systems Configuration Study, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 60)
    Drawdowns; Army Corps of Engineers
  - Salvage Timber Sales, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Nez Perce National Forest; Forest Health; Timber Salvage
  - Saving-Exempt Income Tax, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    American Business Conference; Congressional Budget Office; Income Tax; Banks and Banking
  - Savings and Loans Litigation, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Savings Bill, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Savings Accounts; Banks and Banking
  - Savings Propensity, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Savings Accounts; Baby Boom Generation; Banks and Banking
  - Savings Propensity, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Savings Accounts; Baby Boom Generation; Retirement; Individual Retirement Accounts; Banks and Banking
  - Savings Propensity, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Saylor Creek Boming Range, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Mountain Air Force Base; Saylor Creek Range
  - School Choice, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Public Schools; Education
  - School to Work, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    School to Work Opportunities Act; Education
    H.R.2884
  - Seawolf Submarine, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Nuclear Submarines
  - Secretary of Education, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Riley, Richard
  - Securities Reform, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    North America Development Bank see NAFTA; Securities Private Enforcement Reform Act; Banks and Banking
    Torres, Esteban E.; Tauzin, Billy
    H.R.5828; H.R.417
  - Securities Reform Act, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    S.1699; H.R.3227
  - Seeds, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Grass Seed; Rogers NK Seed Company
  - Selective Service, 1991-1994 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Selective Service System; Draft--History
  - Semiconductor Industry Association, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Internal Revenue Code; Semiconductors
  - Service Station Dealer Issues, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Sinclair Oil Corporation; Petroleum Marketing Competition Enhancement Act; Gasoline Dealerships
    H.R.2966; H.R.2600; S.672; S.790
  - Sexual Harassment, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Women's Political Caucus
  - Shepody Seed Potatoes, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Shoshone Indian Judgment, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Shoshone Indians; Indians of North America--Land Claims
    H.R.3384
  - Silver Valley, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Wallace, Idaho; Federal Bureau of Investigation; Shoshone County, Idaho; Gambling; Department of Commerce
  - Skaggs Task Force, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Congressional Reforms; Democratic Party
  - Ski Areas, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    Schwitzer Ski Resort; Bogus Basin Ski Resort; Ski Resorts
  - Small Business, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    Small Businesses--Constituent Communication; Consumer Protection; Mandated Family and Medical Leave Bill
    H.R.2; H.R.1470
  - Small Business, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Snails, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    Bruneau Snail; Idaho Farm Bureau
  - Snake River Alliance, 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    Military Conscientious Objector Act of 1992; Pacifism; Persian Gulf War; Nuclear Disarmament; Nuclear Contamination; Boise Peace Quilt Project
  - Social Security, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Social Security, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Social Security, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Social Security Administration, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    H.R.4277; P.L.103-296
  - Soil Conservation Service, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    Wetlands;Agriculture
  - Somalia, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Somalia, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Somalia, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - South Africa, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    Apartheid; Economic Sanctions
  - South Canyon Fire, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    Glenwood Springs, Colorado; Storm King Mountain; Forest Fires; Firefighters; Forest Health
    Thrash, Jim; Roth, Roger
  - Soviet Agriculture Aid, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    Soviet Union; Russia; Economic Assistance
  - Space Station, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    NASA; Space Stations; United States--Budget
    H.R.4489
  - Space Station, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    NASA; Space Stations
  - Speech: Idaho Cable Television Association, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Education; Student Loan Reform Act
  - Speech: NEA Conference, 1992 Feb. 15 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    National Education Association; Idaho Education Association; Education
  - Sportsman's Caucus, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Hunting; National Rifle Association; Omnibus Crime Control Act
    H.R.1815
  - Statehood Process, 1991; (1955) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Stewardship Bill, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Land Management; Ecosystems; National Forest Stewardship Contracting Act; Forest Health; Endangered Species Act
    Position Statement on the Endangered Species Act, Jan 1994
  - Stewardship Contracting, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Land Use; Timber Sales; Forest Health
    Statement before Subcommittee on Specialty Crops and Natural Resources 9/29/1994
  - Stewardship Projects, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Land Use; Forest Health; Forest Service; Timber
  - Stewardship Workshop, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Land Use; Public Lands
  - Stock Options: Financial Accounting Standards Board, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Stockpile, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Department of Defense; National Defense Stockpile; Silver
    H.R.2599
  - Stormwater, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Cancer; Water Pollution
  - Strategic Defense Initiative, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Persian Gulf War; Star Wars see Strategic Defense Initiative
  - Strategic Material Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Defense; Natural Resources
  - Striker Protection Act, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Workplace Fairness Act; Trade-Unions; Strikes and Lockouts; National Labor Relations Act
    H.R.5
  - Striker Protection Act, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    Workplace Fairness Act; Trade-Unions; Strikes and Lockouts
  - Student Financial Aid, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    Student Loans; Scholarships; Grants; Education
  - Student Loans, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    United Negro College Fund; Education
  - Sturgeon, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    Fish and Wildlife Service
  - Sugarbeet Growers, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    Sugarbeets; NAFTA
  - Sugarbeet Growers, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    Sugarbeets; Mexico--Sugar
  - Superconducting Super Collider, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    Morrison Knudsen Corporation
  - Superfund, 1991-1994 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Superfund, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    Superfund Reform Act
    H.R.3800
  - Syria, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Taft Tunnel, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    Wallace, Idaho; Idaho--Tourist Trade
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    China; GATT; International Relations
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    International Relations; Silver; Sunshine Mining Company
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    International Trade; Fishing--Pacific Ocean; International Relations
    H.R.2920
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    Statement on floor, "Republic of China" 10/2/1991
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Taiwan, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    Idaho; International Relations
  - Taiwan, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Targhee Resort, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    Targhee National Forest; Teton Valley, Idaho
  - Task Force on Homelessness, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    Homeless
  - Tax Fairness and Economic Growth Act, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Income Tax; Pension; Labor Unions; Collective Bargaining; Federal Express
    H.R.4210
  - Tax Refund Anticipation Loans, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Tax Refunds; Banks and Banking
  - Taxes: Retroactivity and Constitution, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Taylor/Wolf: Religious Response, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Christian Coalition
  - Teacher in Space Program, 1992-1994 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    NASA
    Morgan, Barbara
  - Telecommunication Carrier Assistance, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Network Communication; Wiretapping; Communication Systems; Public Lands; American Civil Liberties Union
    H.R.4922
  - Telecommunications, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Telecommunications Industry; Information Networks; Micron Technology, Inc.; Japan--Trade; International Trade
  - Telecommunications Research, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Telecommunications Equipment; Research and Manufacturing; Competition Act; Information Networks
    H.R.1527; H.R.3515
  - Term Limits, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Term Limits, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Term Limits, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Congressional Tenure
  - The Arts--Congressional Activities, 1992-1994 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    National Botanic Garden; Music; American Arts Alliance; National Endowment for the Arts; Idaho--Arts
  - Tibet, 1990-1994 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Timber, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    NAFTA: International Trade; Timber Industry
  - Timber, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Timber Salvage, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    Spotted Owl; Forest Health
  - Timber: Canadian Imports, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    Canada--Lumber
  - Timber: Christmas Trees, undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
    National Christmas Tree Association, Inc.
  - Timber: Clearcutting, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Natural Resources Committee; Subcommittee on National Parks, Forests and Public Lands; Clearcutting; Forest Reserves; Timber Industry
    Bryant, John
    H.R.1164
  - Timber: Companies, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    Potlatch; Plum Creek; Salmon; Timber Industry
  - Timber: Costs, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    Espy, Mike; Clinton, Bill
  - Timber: Economics, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Timber: Environmental Blocks, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Timber Industry; Earth First!; Sierra Club; Forest Reserves--Environmental Aspects
  - Timber: Forestry: General, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Timber: High Quality Forestry, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    Timber Industry; Forest Reserves; Washington--Forest Reserves; Spotted Owls
    Kuehne, H.J. "Gene"
  - Timber: Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    Potlatch Corp; Clearcutting; Endangered Species Act
  - Timber: Seven Point Plan on Timber, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Timber: Specific Sales/Projects, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Timber: Supply: General, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Tourism, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    Rural Development; Idaho--Tourist Trade; Fairfield, Idaho; Rural Tourism Foundation
    Roe, Robert
  - Tourism, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    Tourist Trade; Recreation
  - Tourism, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    Ecology; Rural Development; Tourist Trade; Commerce Department; Tourist Trade; Idaho--Tourist Trade
  - Tourism, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    Recreation; Tourist Trade; Travel; Public Lands; Idaho--Tourist Trade
    H.Con.Res.110
  - Tourism, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    Travel; Recreation; Idaho--Tourist Trade; Idaho Outfitters and Guides Association; Natural Resources
  - Tourism, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    Tourist Trade; Idaho--Tourist Trade
  - Tourism: Caucus Membership, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    Tourist Trade
  - Tourism: Silver Valley, Idaho, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    Tourist Trade; American Folklife Center; Silver Valley, Idaho
  - Tourism: Silver Valley, Idaho, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    Mines and Mining; American Folklife Center; National Heritage Corridor; Idaho--Tourist Trade
  - Trade Development Program: Wyden Mexico Trip, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    NAFTA; Bunker Hill Superfund; Mexico--Mines and Mining; Chile--Mines and Mining; Coeur d'Alene Mines
  - Trade Unions, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Firefighters; Amalgamated Transit Union; Railroad Workers; Right-to-Work; United Food and Commercial Workers; Health Security Act; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; United Transportation Union
    H.R.5; H.R.3866
  - Trails: Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Oregon Trail
  - Trails: Symm's Bill, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Blue Ribbon Coalition; Motorized Vehicles
    S.1204; Surface Transportation Efficiency Act; H.R.1155; National Recreational Trails Fund Act of 1991
  - Training Range, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Mountain Home Air Force Base; Owyhee County, Idaho; Idaho Fish and Game; Bombing Ranges--Environmental Aspects; Bureau of Land Management; Bombing Ranges--Economic Aspects; Wildlife
    Andrus, Cecil
  - Training Range, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Mountain Home Air Force Base; Saylor Creek Bombing Range; Military Land Reform and Reassessment Act; Bombing Ranges--Environmental Aspects; Bombing Ranges--Economic Aspects; Wildlife
  - Transportation, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Amtrak; Union Pacific; Railroads; National Transportation System; Transportation--Budgets; Department of Commerce
  - Transportation, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Amtrak; Interstate Commerce Commission
  - Transportation, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Merchant Marine; Department of Commerce
    H.R.4003
  - Transportation, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Trucking; Federal Aviation Administration; National Transportation; Idaho--Transportation; Department of Commerce
  - Transportation, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Airports; Roads; Motorcycles; National Highway Safety; Department of Commerce
  - Transportation Department, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    National Scenic Byways Program; Tourist Trade; Roads; Idaho--Roads; Boise City--Roads; Wallace, Idaho; Air Traffic Controllers
  - Travel and Tourism, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Tourist Trade; Idaho--Tourist Trade; Department of Commerce
  - Tribal Issues, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Indians of North America; Reservations--Water Quality
  - Truth-in-Saving, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Federal Deposit Insurance; Savings; Credit Unions; Banks and Banking
    P.L.102-242
  - Turkey, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    H.R.4399
  - Uganda, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Unfunded Federal Mandates, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Natural Resources; Environmental Protection Agency; Education--Federal Policies
  - Unfunded Federal Mandates, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Railroads; Idaho Public Utilities Commission
  - United Egg Producers, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Egg Products Inspection Act; Egg Production Industry
  - United Nations, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Japan; Persian Gulf War
  - United Nations, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - United Nations, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    United Nations--Armed Forces
  - United Nations: War Crimes Tribunal, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - University of Idaho, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Agriculture--Budgets; University of Idaho--College of Agriculture
  - University of Idaho, College of Agriculture, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    Zinser, Elizabeth